Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES V. Affiliates, 1930-80 (Part 1)
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES V. AFFILIATES (PART 1)
  - Uniform Accounting and Financial Reporting, A Supplementary Guide for the Small Affiliate PPFA, Inc., 9/1967 (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - Affiliates General
    - Accounting Uniform, Guide, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Affiliates, Affirmative Action Policy
      - 1971-1974 (Box 137, Folder 6)
      - 1975-1978 (Box 137)
    - National Affiliates: Anti-Poverty Program, 1965-1966 (Box 137, Folder 7)
    - Affiliate Performance Report, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 8)
    - National Affiliates: Application for Reaffiliation, 1963-1966 (Box 137, Folder 9)
    - Affiliates General: Audits, Definition of an Audit, 1976 (Box 137, Folder 10)
    - Affiliates General: Auxiliaries, 1972 (Box 137, Folder 11)
    - National Affiliates: "Big Push," 1959-1961 (Box 137, Folder 12)
    - Black Personnel, 1970 (Box 137, Folder 13)
    - Board of Directors
      - Alabama thru Hawaii, 1967-1970 (Box 137, Folder 14)
      - Illinois thru Minnesota, 1968-1969 (Box 137, Folder 15)
      - Missouri thru New York, 1965-1970 (Box 137, Folder 16)
      - North Carolina thru Pennsylvania, 1962-1970 (Box 137, Folder 17)
      - Rhode Island thru Wyoming, 1967-1970 (Box 137, Folder 18)
      - Bylaws, Sample Bylaws, 1960-1972 (Box 137, Folder 19)
      - Affiliate/Chapter Agreements from 1974
        - 1974 (Box 137, Folder 20)
        - 1975 (Box 137)
      - Chapter Incorporation Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978 (Box 137, Folder 21)
    - Chapter from 1973
      - 1973-1974 (Box 137, Folder 22)
      - 1975-1978 (Box 137)
    - Charter Amending Lobbying Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978 (Box 137, Folder 23)
    - Changes in Affiliate Status
      - 1971-1974 (Box 137, Folder 24)
      - 1975-1979 (Box 137)
      - 1981 (Box 137, Folder 25)
    - Changes in Names, Addresses, etc. in Affiliates, 1970-1973 (Box 137, Folder 26)
    - Coalition, Legal (Paul, Eve) (Voter Education), 1978 (Box 137, Folder 27)
    - Affiliate Count and Lists by Region and Status from 1969
      - 1969-1974 (Box 137, Folder 28)
      - 1979 (Box 137)
    - Checklist for Affiliates I and E Programs 1973, undated (Box 137, Folder 29)
    - Clinical Investigation Program
      - Affiliates General: PPFA Clinical Investigation Program by Sarah Tietze, 5/12/1960 (Box 137, Folder 30)
      - PPFA National: CIP Monthly Reports, 1960-1962 (Box 137, Folder 31)
      - Clinical Investigation Program, Budgets, 1958-1963 (Box 137, Folder 32)
      - PPFA National: CIP Forms, Records, etc., 1958-1963 (Box 137, Folder 33)
      - PPFA National
        - Clinics, Fees, 1967-1968 (Box 137, Folder 34)
        - Clinics, General, 1956-1968 (Box 137, Folder 35)
    - Coercion, 1973 (Box 137, Folder 36)
    - Confidentiality, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978-1979 (Box 137, Folder 37)
  - National Affiliates: Confidentiality Statement
    - 1968-1974 (Box 137, Folder 38)
    - 1975-1979 (Box 137)
  - Affiliates General: Consumer Participation in Affiliate Decision-Making from 1973
    - 1973 (Box 137, Folder 39)
    - 1975-1979 (Box 137)
  - Contraceptives - Survey-73 Centers
    - Contraceptives, 1961 Survey of 73 Centers, 1961-1962 (Box 137, Folder 40)
    - Contraceptives, 1961 Methods Survey, 1961-1962 (Box 137, Folder 41)
  - Affiliates General
    - Affiliate Contributions, 1970 (Box 137, Folder 42)
    - Affiliates Cooperation with Junior Leagues, A Survey 1965, 1966 (Box 137, Folder 43)
    - Count of Cities with Affiliate Clinics, 1970 (Box 137, Folder 44)
    - Direct Services Provided by National Staff for Affiliates, 1971 (Box 137, Folder 45)
    - The Diffusion of a Population Related Innovation; the Planned Parenthood Affiliate By L. A. Brown and S. O. Gustavus, undated (Box 137, Folder 46)
    - Directory of PP Affiliate Clinics, 1957-1970 (Box 137, Folder 47)
    - 1970 Directory of PP Affiliates and Clinical Locations, 1970 (Box 137, Folder 48)
    - Discrimination from 1974
      - 1974 (Box 137, Folder 49)
      - 1975-1979 (Box 137)
    - Drug Dispensing, Pharmacy Boards, State Laws, Prophylactics (Box 137)
      - Drug Dispensing, Pharmacy Boards, State Laws, 1964-1979 (Box 137, Folder 50)
      - Drug Dispensing, Miscellaneous, Correspondence, 1975 (Box 137, Folder 51)
      - Prophylactic Laws: City, State and Pharmacy Boards (1971-1977) MISSING (Box 137)
    - Affiliates, Dues, Payments Less than 8% for 1971, 1971 (Box 137, Folder 52)
    - Executive Directors' Orientation, 1975-1979 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Emergency Guidance Groups, 1960 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Executive Directors' Orientation Evaluations, 1975-1979 (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Fair Share, Correspondence from 1973
      - 1973-1974 (Box 138, Folder 4)
      - 1975-1979 (Box 138)
    - Fair Share, 1979, 1978 (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Fair Share, 1978, 1977-1978 (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - Fair Share, 1977, 1977 (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - Fair Share, 1980 (Box 138, Folder 8)
    - Fair Share, Preliminary Fair Share Chart
      - 1974 (Box 138, Folder 9)
      - 1979 (Box 138)
    - Fair Share Formula, 1973 (Box 138, Folder 10)
    - Proposed Affiliate Fair Share Plan, 5/31/1972 (Box 138, Folder 11)
    - Proposed Affiliate Fair Share Plan, 1972 (Box 138, Folder 12)
    - Proposed Rev. Affiliates Fair Share, 1975 (Box 138, Folder 12a)
    - Proposed Rev. Affiliates Fair Share, 1976 (Box 138, Folder 12b)
    - Revision of the Fair Share Plan, 1975 (Box 138, Folder 12c)
    - Proposed Revision, Affiliate Fair Share Plan, 1978 (Box 138, Folder 13)
    - Affiliate, Financial Information, 1970-1971, undated (Box 138, Folder 14)
    - Forms
      - 1972-1974 (Box 138, Folder 15)
      - 1975-1980 (Box 138)
    - Fund Raising (Affiliates), 1971 (Box 138, Folder 16)
    - General, Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 138, Folder 17)
    - General, Correspondence, 1954-1969 (Box 138, Folder 18)
    - Government Funding Questionnaire, 1976 (Box 138, Folder 19)
    - Government Reporting Requirements, 1976 (Box 138, Folder 20)
    - Guide for a Three-Year Plan, 1974 (Box 138, Folder 21)
    - Guidelines for the Evaluation of the Affiliate Executive Director (NEDC), 1976 (Box 138, Folder 22)
    - Guidelines for the Evaluation of the Affiliate Executive Director (NEDC), 1977 (Box 138, Folder 23)
    - Guidelines for Affiliates: Initiating Medical Services, 1972 (Box 138, Folder 24)
    - Guidelines for Affiliate I and E Committees and Affiliate Volunteer I and E Program, undated (Box 138, Folder 25)
    - Guidelines for Affiliate: Personnel Practices, 1975 (Box 138, Folder 26)
    - Guidelines for Keeping Pregnancy Counseling Records, 1978 (Box 138, Folder 27)
    - PPFA Handbook, 1970 (Box 138, Folder 28)
    - Affiliates Historical Survey
      - 1967-1974 (Box 138, Folder 29)
      - 1974-1980 (Box 138)
    - Executive Directors Job Assessment Survey, 1977 (Box 138, Folder 30)
    - Affiliates History, Tennessee, 1940-1976 (Box 138, Folder 31)
    - Affiliates I and E Handbook, 1972 (Box 138, Folder 32)
    - Improvement in Affiliate Nat'l Staff Communications, 1970 (Donald F. Stern, Darl H. Todd), 1970 (Box 138, Folder 33)
    - Affiliate Income, 1969-1977-1978, 1978 (Box 138, Folder 34)
    - Affiliate Income, 1969-1976, 1976 (Box 138, Folder 35)
    - Indigenous Neighborhood Workers, 1965-1973 (Box 138, Folder 36)
    - Informed Consent from 1973, 1953-1974 (Box 138, Folder 37)
    - Initial Steps Necessary for Organizing A Planned Parenthood Affiliate, 1964 (Box 138, Folder 38)
    - Inter-Affiliate Statistical Report and Summary, 1969-1970 (Box 138, Folder 39)
    - Affiliate Involvement in Joint and/or Cooperative Activities from 1971
      - 1971 (Box 138, Folder 40)
      - 1977 (Box 138)
    - Changes in Affiliate Status from 1/1981 MISSING (Box 138, Folder 41)
    - List of Affiliate/Chapter Presidents and Executive Directors from 1970
      - 1969-1974 (Box 138, Folder 42)
      - 1975-1980 (Box 138)
    - List of Affiliates which are not OEO Funded, 1971 (Box 138, Folder 43)
    - List of Legal counsel of all Affiliates, 1967-1972 (Box 138, Folder 44)
    - Loan Fund, 1970 (Box 138, Folder 45)
    - Meeting, Information Systems for Affiliates, 1978 (Box 138, Folder 46)
    - Status Report on PPFA's Meeting Information System for Affiliates, 1977 (Box 138, Folder 47)
    - Medicaid, Medi-cal Reimbursement (Title XIX)
      - 1969-1974 (Box 138, Folder 48)
      - 1979 (Box 138)
    - Medical Checklist (Medical Site Visitor), 1978 (Box 138, Folder 49)
    - Medical Directors/Medical Advisory Chairmen In Medical Affiliates, 1971-1973 (Box 138, Folder 50)
    - Medical Directors/Medical Advisory Committee, 1976 (Box 138, Folder 51)
    - Affiliate Medical Reviews, 1976 (Box 138, Folder 52)
    - Medical Training Agreements between Affiliate, Medical, Residency Programs, 1972 (Box 138, Folder 53)
    - Memos to general, 1964-1972 (Box 138, Folder 54)
    - Minimum Dues formula, 1971 (Box 138, Folder 55)
    - Federation, Trends, Services, Methods, Costs, Income (President's report), 1979 (Box 138, Folder 56)
    - Fee Schedules
      - 1964-1974 (Box 138, Folder 57)
      - 1975-1979 (Box 138)
    - Fees Analysis of Patient Fees Compared to Total Income
      - 1973-1976 (Box 138, Folder 58)
      - 1977 (Box 138)
    - List of Affiliates Established in New or Renovated Quarters, 1972 (Box 138, Folder 59)
    - Affiliates Fact Book from Nov. 1962, Correspondence (Box 138, Folder 60)
    - Affiliates Financial Reporting, 1972 (Box 138, Folder 61)
    - Prophylactic Laws, City, State and Pharmacy Boards
      - 1972 (Box 138, Folder 62)
      - 1977 (Box 138)
  - Mobile Units (Box 138)
    - PPFA National: Medical Coaches, See: Mobile Units from 1959, 1961-1970 (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - PPWP National Affiliates General: Mobile Units (Box 139)
      - 1966-1974 (Box 139, Folder 2)
      - 1977 (Box 139)
    - Alabama, Mobile Units, 1967 (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - California, Mobile Units, 1963-1966 (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Colorado, Mobile Units, 1963-1964 (Box 139, Folder 5)
    - Illinois, Mobile Units, 1961-1963 (Box 139, Folder 6)
    - Maryland, Mobile Units, 1968 (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - New York City, Mobile Units, 1965-1967 (Box 139, Folder 8)
    - New York State, Mobile Units, 1963-1965 (Box 139, Folder 9)
    - Ohio, Mobile Units, 1965 (Box 139, Folder 10)
    - Pennsylvania, Mobile Units, 1962-1966 (Box 139, Folder 11)
    - Rhode Island, Mobile Units, 1964 (Box 139, Folder 12)
    - Texas, Mobile Units, 1963-1967 (Box 139, Folder 13)
    - Washington, Mobile Units, 1964 (Box 139, Folder 14)
    - PPFA: Mobile Units, Miscellaneous, 1961-1965 (Box 139, Folder 15)
  - Affiliates General
    - Nurse Practitioners, 1975-1981 (Box 139, Folder 16)
    - Nurse Clinicians, Nurse Specialists from 1971
      - 1971-1974 (Box 139, Folder 17)
      - 1976 (Box 139)
    - Omnibus from 1972
      - 1972-1973 (Box 139, Folder 18)
      - 1976-1978 (Box 139)
    - Omnibus, 1971 (Box 139, Folder 19)
  - PPFA National
    - Operation Evaluation, Program, Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 139, Folder 20)
    - Operation Evaluation, Program, General and Mimeos from 1966 (Box 139, Folder 21)
    - Operational Levels Committee, Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 139, Folder 22)
    - Organization Outline for Statewide Public Affairs Committee, 1972 (Box 139, Folder 23)
    - Paramedical Programs, 1972-1973 (Box 139, Folder 24)
    - Patient's Bill of Rights from 1974, 1975 (Box 139, Folder 25)
    - Patient Education, 1974 (Box 139, Folder 26)
    - Patient Relations Committee, 1977 (Box 139, Folder 27)
    - Patient Service, Proportion of Total Expenditures, 1968-1969 (Box 139, Folder 28)
    - Physicians Compensation, Legal, Accounting (Paul Eve; Diaz, Andy), 1978-1979 (Box 139, Folder 29)
    - Affiliates Planning, 1973-1974 (Box 139, Folder 30)
    - Profiles of Affiliate Members of Executive Directors Council, 1970 (Box 139, Folder 31)
    - Public Affairs and Affiliate Action, 1976-1977 (Box 139, Folder 32)
    - Questionnaire on Government Funding, 1976 (Box 139, Folder 33)
    - Affiliates' Research
      - 1974 (Box 139, Folder 34)
      - 1975-1979 (Box 139)
      - 1970-1973 (Box 139, Folder 35)
      - 1962-1971 (Box 139, Folder 36)
  - Affiliates General
    - Affiliates' Research, Community and Family Study Center, Summer Workshop, 1964 (Box 139, Folder 37)
    - Affiliates' Research Community and Family Study Center, 1962 (Box 139, Folder 38)
  - PPFA National: Affiliates' Research, General, Mimeos, etc., 1962-1972 (Box 139, Folder 39)
  - Affiliates General
    - Affiliates' Research, HEW Guidelines for Medical Research, 10/9/1973 (Box 139, Folder 40)
    - Affiliates Research, IUD: Spermicidal Barrier Contraceptive, 1979 (Box 139, Folder 41)
    - Affiliates' Research, ISR Project, 1969-1971 (Box 139, Folder 42)
    - Affiliates' Research, San Antonio, 1971-1972 (Box 139, Folder 43)
    - Affiliates' Research, Standards for PP Bio-Medical Research, 1970 (Box 139, Folder 44)
    - Affiliates' Research, Standards for Social Science Research, 1973 (Box 139, Folder 45)
    - Retention of Medical Records, 1977 (Box 139, Folder 46)
    - Affiliates' Review; Team Review, 1976 (Box 139, Folder 47)
    - The Role of the Local Clergyman in PP, to PP Personnel Who Seek the Cooperation of the Clergy, 1950 (Box 139, Folder 48)
    - PPWP Affiliates General: Rural Health Initiatives (RHI), 1978 (Box 139, Folder 49)
    - Salary Range from 1974
      - 1974 (Box 139, Folder 50)
      - 1975-1977 (Box 139)
    - Services
      - Abortion-Pregnancy Counseling, 1976-1979 (Box 139, Folder 51)
      - Abortion-Pregnancy and Abortion Counseling from 1971
        - 1970-1974 (Box 139, Folder 52)
        - 1975 (Box 139)
      - Affiliates Which Pay for Services but Do Not Operate Clinics, 1972 (Box 139, Folder 53)
      - The Blind, 1972 (Box 139, Folder 54)
      - Cancer Screening, 1976-1978 (Box 139, Folder 55)
      - Child Abuse, Maltreatment Reporting, 1979 (Box 139, Folder 56)
      - Child Health Assurance, 1979 (Box 139, Folder 57)
      - Colposeopy, Ocryosurgery, 1978-1979 (Box 139, Folder 58)
      - Comprehensive Health Care, 1978 (Box 139, Folder 59)
      - Comprehensive Health Exams, 1977 (Box 139, Folder 60)
      - Condom Program
        - 1972-1974 (Box 139, Folder 61)
        - 1978 (Box 139)
      - Drop-In Clinics, 1971 (Box 139, Folder 62)
      - Genetic Counseling, 1976-1978 (Box 139, Folder 63)
      - The Handicapped from 1973
        - 1973-1974 (Box 139, Folder 64)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 139)
      - Infertility from 1971
        - 1956-1974 (Box 139, Folder 65)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 139)
      - Institutional (Correctional, Etc.), 1972-1973 (Box 139, Folder 66)
      - Intern and Nurses' Training
        - 1971 (Box 139, Folder 67)
        - 1975 (Box 139)
      - Males from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 139, Folder 68)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 139)
      - Menstrual Extraction
        - 1974 (Box 139, Folder 69)
        - 1975 (Box 139)
      - Mentally Retarded
        - 1972-1974 (Box 139, Folder 70)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 139)
      - Mexican-Americans, 1978 (Box 139, Folder 71)
      - Minors, Teenagers, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978-1979 (Box 139, Folder 72)
      - Minors, Teenagers from 1975
        - 1974 (Box 139, Folder 73)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 139)
      - Minors, Teenagers, 1967-1974 (Box 139, Folder 74)
      - Teenagers, Minors, Medical Department, Memos, State Laws, Reports, General
        - 1968-1974 (Box 140, Folder 1)
        - 1977-1980 (Box 140)
        - Survey of Affiliates Policy on Service to Minors, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 2)
        - "Delivery of Contraception Information and Services to Teenagers," Miller and Jones, New York Department of Health, Health Research Training Program, Summer 1971 (1971) (Box 140, Folder 3)
      - Nutrition Components
        - 1973 (Box 140, Folder 4)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 140)
      - Post Menopausal Screening, 1979 (Box 140, Folder 5)
      - Affiliates Offering IUDs, 1964 (Box 140, Folder 6)
      - Affiliates Offering Family Planning Counseling in Local Hospitals, 1971-1973 (Box 140, Folder 7)
      - Pregnancy Testing from 1973
        - 1973 (Box 140, Folder 8)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 140)
      - Pre-Natal Care from 1975
        - 1974 (Box 140, Folder 9)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 140)
      - Rhythm Clinics, 1972 (Box 140, Folder 10)
      - Rubella Screening; Immunization, 1978-1979 (Box 140, Folder 11)
      - Sex Education from 1972
        - 1972-1974 (Box 140, Folder 12)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 140)
      - Sex Therapy, 1977 (Box 140, Folder 13)
      - Shopping Centers, 1972 (Box 140, Folder 14)
      - Sickle Cell Disease Testing
        - 1971-1973 (Box 140, Folder 15)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 140)
      - Sterilization, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1979 (Box 140, Folder 16)
      - Sterilization
        - 1970-1974 (Box 140, Folder 17)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 140)
      - Unmarried Clients, 1973 (Box 140, Folder 18)
      - Vasectomy from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 140, Folder 19)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 140)
      - Venereal Disease Screening and Treatment
        - 1969-1974 (Box 140, Folder 20)
        - 1976-1978 (Box 140)
    - Sperm Banks from 1972
      - 1972 (Box 140, Folder 21)
      - 1975-1978 (Box 140)
    - Affiliates' Staff Manual, 5/1968 (Box 140, Folder 22)
    - Standard Operating Procedure, 1977 (Box 140, Folder 23)
    - Summary of Affiliate Expenditures for Supplies and Equipment, Medical Services Rendered (Base Year-1974), undated (Box 140, Folder 24)
    - Summary of PP Policies and Fees, 11/3/1964 (Box 140, Folder 25)
    - Surveys
      - Executive Directors Salary Survey, 1973 (Box 140, Folder 26)
      - NEDC Personnel Practices Survey, 1973-74 (Box 140, Folder 27)
      - Survey of Executive Directors, 1977 (Box 140, Folder 28)
      - Survey, Personnel Practices and Salary Levels: A Comparative Survey of PP Affiliates, Esther Gold, Cecile Steinberg, NEDC, 1978 (Box 140, Folder 29)
      - Survey, A Profile of Planned Parenthood Executive Directors, 1977 (Box 140, Folder 30)
      - PPFA, 1980, Program Evaluation and Planning Survey, 1980-1981 (Box 140, Folder 31)
      - Public Opinion Surveys on Abortion Backgrounder, 1981 (Box 140, Folder 32)
      - Survey of Affiliate Abortion-Related Activities, 1970-1972 (Box 140, Folder 33)
      - Survey of Affiliate Sex Education Programs, Recommendations and Needs, 1977 (Box 140, Folder 34)
      - Survey on the Miscellaneous and Bulk Purchasing, 1977 (Box 140, Folder 35)
      - Survey of Minority Group Participation in PP Programs, 1966 (Box 140, Folder 36)
      - Survey, Part-Pay Clinic Programs, 1973 (Box 140, Folder 37)
      - Racial and Ethnic Profile Survey, 1975-1977 (Box 140, Folder 38)
      - Survey of Roman Catholics in Planned Parenthood Affiliate Program, 1964, undated (Box 140, Folder 39)
      - Telephone Survey, 1971 (Box 140, Folder 40)
    - Affiliates's Tax Exemption, 1968 (Box 140, Folder 41)
    - Title IV A, Funds
      - 1971-1974 (Box 140, Folder 42)
      - 1975 (Box 140)
    - Title V, 1977 (Box 140, Folder 43)
    - Title X, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978-1979 (Box 140, Folder 44)
    - Title X from 1975
      - 1973 (Box 140, Folder 45)
      - 1975-1980 (Box 140)
    - Title X; Remark of Faye Wattleton at News Conference, Washington D.C., 10/10/1978, [Outcard for Title XIX] (Box 140, Folder 46)
    - Title XX Funds, 1975-1978 (Box 140, Folder 47)
    - "To Determine The Cost of a Clinic Visit", By Mrs. John W. Brown, Jr., 1968 (Box 140, Folder 48)
    - Affiliates, Turf, 1975-1976 (Box 140, Folder 49)
    - "Uniform Accounting and Financial Reporting, A Supplemental Guide for Small Affiliates," 1967 (Box 140, Folder 50)
    - "Uniform Accounting and Financial Reporting, Accounting for O.E.O. Grants," 10/1967 (Box 140, Folder 51)
    - United Fund, 1971 (Box 140, Folder 52)
    - United Fund Allocation from United Fund and Funds Budgeted/Permitted, 1971-1972 (Box 140, Folder 53)
    - Members In the United Fund or Local Community Chest, 1972 (Box 140, Folder 54)
    - For the Affiliate Exploring United Way Membership, 1973, Revision, 1975
      - 1973 (Box 140, Folder 55)
      - 1975 (Box 140)
    - United Way Questionnaire, Evaluation of Resources Affiliates with Membership, 1977 (Box 140, Folder 56)
    - Workshops for Affiliate Presidents, undated (Box 140, Folder 57)
    - Worksheet on Long-Range Planning Priorities for Your Affiliate, 1970 (Box 140, Folder 58)
    - Yearly Growth of PP Affiliate Programs, 1960 through 1973, 1972-1974 (Box 140, Folder 59)
  - Alabama
    - Anti-Poverty, 1966-1973 (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - Alabama Council for Voluntary Family Planning, 1971-1972 (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - Contacts from 1965 (Box 141)
      - 1965-1972 (Box 141, Folder 3)
      - 1975 (Box 141)
    - Hospitals, 1964-1967 (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - Legal, 1958-1970 (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - Migrants, 1968-1969 (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - Proclamation By the Governor: Voluntary Family Planning Week, Week of 4/15/1974 (Box 141, Folder 7)
    - Public Health from 1959
      - 1964-1971 (Box 141, Folder 8)
      - 1977 (Box 141)
    - Public Welfare, 1964-1970 (Box 141, Folder 9)
    - United Fund, United Community Services, 1968-1970 (Box 141, Folder 10)
    - Statewide Family Planning Workshop for PP Affiliates in Alabama, Montgomery, 2/16-17/1972 (Box 141, Folder 11)
    - Schools, General from 1962
      - 1964-1973 (Box 141, Folder 12)
      - 1976 (Box 141)
    - Tuskegee Institute, 1953-1973 (Box 141, Folder 13)
    - University of Alabama, 1966-1970 (Box 141, Folder 14)
    - Birmingham
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1949
        - 1960-1972 (Box 141, Folder 15)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 141)
      - Affiliation, PP League, Correspondence from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 141, Folder 16)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 141)
      - Affiliation, PP League, Correspondence, 1960-1969 (Box 141, Folder 17)
      - PP Birmingham Area, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1979 (Box 141, Folder 18)
      - PP Birmingham Area, Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1977 (Box 141, Folder 19)
      - PP League from 1969
        - 1969-1974 (Box 141, Folder 20)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 141)
        - 1964-1968 (Box 141, Folder 21)
      - Field Trips, 1957-1965 (Box 141, Folder 22)
      - Birmingham PP League, Reports, Clinics, 1964-1969 (Box 141, Folder 23)
      - Birmingham PP League, Reports, General, from 1960
        - 1969 (Box 141, Folder 24)
        - 1976 (Box 141)
      - Birmingham PP League, Reports, Members from 1960
        - 1960-1972 (Box 141, Folder 25)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 141)
      - PP League, Publicity, 1962-1972 (Box 141, Folder 26)
      - PP League of Alabama, Chapters, 1967-1971 (Box 141, Folder 27)
    - Florence, Shoals PP Association, (chapter), 1972 (Box 141, Folder 28)
    - Huntsville
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1961
        - 1961-1974 (Box 141, Folder 29)
        - 1976-1979 (Box 141)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1961 (Box 141)
        - 1962-1974 (Box 141, Folder 30)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 141)
      - PP Association of Madison County, Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1977 (Box 141, Folder 31)
      - PP Association of Madison County from 1974
        - 1974 (Box 141, Folder 32)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 141)
      - PP Association of Madison County, 1965-1973 (Box 141, Folder 33)
      - PP Association of Madison County, Field Visit Reports, 1977 (Box 141, Folder 34)
      - PP of Madison County, Reports, General from 1966 (Box 141)
        - 1966-1973 (Box 141, Folder 35)
        - 1978 (Box 141)
      - PP of Madison County, Reports, Members from 1966 (Box 141)
        - 1966-1970 (Box 141, Folder 36)
        - 1978 (Box 141)
      - PP of Madison County, Publicity, 1967-1968 (Box 141, Folder 37)
      - Field Trips, 1961-1963 (Box 141, Folder 38)